hello this is a test audio clip for trading your model
it contains different types of arts nouns barbs adjectives numbers dates and even some nonsense the check
the robustness against nice
for example
today is a november so team twenty twenty five
ah serve as or
is sunny but vote but to be and
is increasing up to fifteen metres per second
ah i'm reading this
allowed so can understand how i speak
and now drumroll trotter da da da da da da da da da da
and now drummer
одна он джам роу что та та та та та та та та та та война
trotted out are that are better than that
back to normal
the model
should recognize
this as a part of the training set good luck with training